Sheet1   	  	  	  	  	  	  	  	
  	Last Revised: 10/29/01	Credit Watch List (For Internal Use Only)						
E-rating	Call Credit for approval	E-rating	Call Credit for approval (cont.)	E-rating	NO TRADES	E-rating	NO TRADES	
 11	Abraxas Petroleum Corporation	 11	Mallon Oil Company	 11	Adonis Energy Corporation 	 10	Terra International, Inc.	
 11	ACN Energy, Inc.	 9	Mariner Energy, Inc.	 11	ABQ Energy Group, Ltd.	 10	Terra Nitrogen Corporation (and Limited Partnership)	
 10	Adams Resources Marketing, Ltd.	 7	MarkWest Hydrocarbon, Inc.	 11	Advanced Aromatics, Inc.	 10	Terra Resources, Inc.	
 10	AES New Energy, Inc.	 11	Metromedia Energy, Inc.	 12	AGF, Inc.	 12	Texas*Ohio Energy, Inc. fka Texas-Ohio W	
 11	Agave Energy Company	 11	MG Natural Gas Corp	 12	AGF Direct Gas Sales Sales Inc.	 11	Texican Natural Gas Company	
 9	AK Steel Corporation	 8	Miami Valley Resources	 10	Air Canada	 11	Texoil, Inc.	
 3	Allegheny Ludlum Corporation	 11	Micah-Tech Industries, Inc -WMBE.	 9	Airtran Holdings, Inc.	 12	Tri-Union Development Corporation--Bankruptcy	
 11	Altman Energy Inc.	 9	Midwest United Energy, LLC	 12	Alma Energy Corp.	 7	United Air Lines, Inc.	
 9	Altrade Transaction, LLC	 7	Mieco Inc. (Prompt and 1 month out only)	 9	America West Airlines, Inc.	 11	United States Gypsum Company	
 11	American Central Energy, LLC	 11	Millenium Gas Marketing, LLC	 9	America West Holdings Corp.	 10	Upstream Energy Services, LLC (& Company)	
 10	American Atlas #1, Ltd. LLC	 11	Mississippi Chemical Corporation	 9	American Airlines, Inc.	 10	U.S. Airways	
 9	Aries Resources LLC	 6	MxEnergy.com	 10	AMR Corp.	 10	VAL Group	
 9	Aspect Resources	 9	Mystic River Energy Corporation	 12	Armstrong World Industries, Inc. (and affilitates)	 11	Velsicol Chemical Corporation	
 6	Barrett Resources Corporation	 11	National Energy & Trade, LLC	 11	Aurora Natural Gas, LLC	 12	V-P Energy, Inc.--bankruptcy	
 11	Belden & Blake Corporation	 11	National Fuel Marketing Company, L.L.C.	 11	Barrington Petroleum Ltd.	 11	Weirton Steel Corporation	
 10	Bellwether Exploration Company	 11	Natural Gas Trading Corporation- WMBE	 10	Beaumont Methanol Limited Partnership	 11	West Texas Gas, Inc.	
 11	Berco Resources, Inc.	 4	Nevada Power Company	 11	Bethlehem Steel Corporation	 12	Wheeling-Pittsburgh Corporation	
 9	BHP Copper Inc.	 10	NGTS, LLC	 12	Borden Chemicals and Plastics (& Operating) LP	 12	Wheeling-Pittsburgh Steel Corporation	
 9	Bonavista Petroleum Ltd.	 10	Niagara Mohawk Energy Marketing, Inc. fka	 11	Brigham Exploration Company			
 11	BP Capital Energy Fund LP	 11	Nine Energy Services, LLC - WMBE	 12	Bristol Resources Corporation			
 11	Bravo Natural Resources, Inc.	 11	Northeast Utilities Service Company	 11	C & L Petroleum, Inc.			
 9	Breitburn Energy Comapny LLC	 10	North Texas Gas Partners, Ltd.	 12	Cage Gas Services			
 4	British Airways plc (prompt month only)	 6	NUI Energy Brokers	 11	CEG Energy Options, Inc.			
 11	BWAB, LLC	 11	Onyx Gas Marketing Company, L.C. 	 10	Chautauqua Airlines, Inc.			
 8	Cabot Oil & Gas Corporation	 10	Oxy Vinyls, LP	 12	Chris Thena Inc.			
 8	Cabot Oil & Gas Marketing Corporation	 11	Panaco, Inc.	 11	Coho Energy Inc.			
 9	Callon Petroleum Company	 11	Panther Pipeline, Inc.	 10	Continental Airlines, Inc.			
 11	CanEnerco Energy Services Limited	 11	Paralan Company, The	 11	Contour Energy Co.			
 10	CanWest Gas Supply (USA) Inc.	 11	Patten Energy Enterprises, Inc. - WMBE	 12	Costilla Energy Inc.			
 8	Carrera Gas Company, LLC	 11	Petrous, LLC	 6	Delta Air Lines, Inc.			
 11	Carrizo Oil & Gas Inc.	 11	Petrocom Energy Group Limited	 12	Denbury Energy Services, Inc.			
 9	Castle Power LLC	 8	Petroglyph Energy, Inc.	 11	Eagle Gas Marketing, LLC	**Additions/Revisions to List		
 11	Castle Texas Production Limited Partnership	 6	PG&E Energy Trading-Canada Corp.	 11	Edison Mission Marketing & Trading Inc.			
 7	Central Soya Company, Inc.	 6	PG&E Energy Trading-Gas Corp.	 12	Equinox Oil Company			
 11	Cerrito Gas Marketing Company	 5	Philadelphia Gas Works	 6	Elizabethtown Gas Company, a division….			
 9	CF Industries, Inc.	 9	Plains Gas Farmers Cooperative Society of He	 12	Elysium Energy, LLC			
 9	Cgas Inc	 11	Plains Resources Co	 11	Empire Pipeline Corp.			
 9	CIG Resources Company	 11	Premiere Eneterprises, L.L.C. - WMBE	 11	Euell Energy Resources, Inc. - WMBE			
 11	CIMA Energy LLC	 10	Progas, Inc.	 11	Exploration Partners, Inc.			
 11	Chesapeake Energy Marketing, Inc.	 10	ProLiance Energy, LLC 	 11	Fagadau Energy Corporation			
 11	Clarke-Mobile Counties Gas District	 8	Public Service Company of New Hampshire	 12	Federal-Mogul Corp. (Bankruptcy)			
 7	Clayton Williams Energy, Inc.	 5	Public Service Company of New Mexico (18 months out only)	 11	Gas Services, Inc.			
 10	Cody Energy LLC	 9	Quicksilver Resources, Inc.	 12	Gasco, Inc.	  	  	
 10	Cokinos Natural Gas Company	 9	Quintana Minerals Canada	 12	Golden Prarie Resources LLC			
 6	Columbia Natural Resources, Inc.	 11	Quintana Petroleum Corp	 11	Gothic Energy Corp			
 9	Comstock Oil & Gas, Inc.	 11	R. Byron Roach	 11	Granite City Steel, a division of National Steel			
 7	Connecticut Light and Power Company, The	 11	Rainbow Gas Company	 9	Hallwood Petroleum, Inc.			
 10	Continental Gas Inc.	 8	Redan Futures Ltd.	 11	Hampshire Chemical Corporation			
 10	Continental Resources Inc.	 11	Ritchie Gas Company	 11	Heartland Steel, Inc.			
 8	Cook Inlet Energy Supply	 11	Rio Vista Energy, Ltd.	 11	Henry Petroleum			
 8	Cornerstone Propane, L.P.	 9	RMS Monte Christo LLC	 11	Heritage Gas Services, L.L.C.			
 9	**Co-Steel, Inc.	 9	Royster-Clark Inc.	 12	Holly Sugar Corporation			
 11	Cox & Perkins Exploration, Inc.	 11	Samson Investment Company	 12	Houston Hydrocarbons, Inc.			
 10	Cross Oil Refining & Marketing	 10	Sanchez Oil & Gas Corporation	 12	Imperial Sugar Company			
 10	Crosstex Energy Services, Ltd.	 6	San Diego Gas & Electric Company (Fin trading 3 mo out only)	 11	Inland Production Company			
 9	Crown Central Petroleum	 10	SDS Petroleum Products, Inc.- WMBE	 11	Inland Resources Inc,			
 10	Cumberland Valley Resources, LLC	 6	Select Energy, Inc.	 12	J.C. Energy Resources, Inc. 			
 10	Cypress Natural Gas, LLC	 11	Seminole Energy Services LLC	 11	Jet Blue Airways Corporation			
 8	DDD Energy, Inc	 10	Shoreham Oil & Gas Company Inc.	 10	Kimball Energy Corporation			
 8	Devon Energy Production Company, L.P.	 4	Sierra Pacific Power Company	 11	KNG Energy, Inc.			
 7	Eagle Gas Marketing Company	 10	SGL Carbon, LLC	 11	Laclede Energy Resources, Inc.			
 11	Econnergy Energy Company 	 10	SIGCORP Energy Services, Inc./LLC	 10	Laroche Industries, Inc.			
 10	Elk Point Resources Inc.	 10	Small Ventures U.S.A., L.L.C.	 11	Linder Energy Company			
 11	Empire Natural Gas Corporation 	 11	South Hampton Refining Company	 11	Louisiana General Oil Company			
 11	Encina Gas Marketing, LLC	 5	South Jersey Resources Group LLC	 11	Linder Oil Company, A Partnership			
 11	Energy Dynamics Management Inc.	 11	Southwest Royalties, Inc.	 11	LTV Steel Company, Inc.			
 9	Energy West, Inc.	 11	Spring Resources Inc.	 12	Lyco Energy Corp			
 11	Engineered Carbons	 11	Stalwart Energy Company	 11	M & B Industrial Gas Development Corp.			
 8	Equity Oil Company	 10	Stewart Petroleum Corporation	 12	Michael Petroleum Corporation			
 11	Enserco Energy, Inc.	 10	Stone Energy Corporation	 12	Midway Airlines			
 11	Esenjay Exploration Inc.	 11	Stratum Group LP	 11	National Steel Corporation			
 10	Estate of William G Hellis	 10	Suburban Natural Gas Company	 9	Neumin Production Co.			
 10	Falcon Creek Resources, Inc.	 11	Sulphur River Gathering, L.P.	 12	Northern Alberta Nitrogen Ltd.			
 7	Farmland Industries, Inc.	 11	Summit Energy LLC	 9	Northwest Airlines, Inc.			
 10	Florida Gas Utility	 11	Summit Resources, Inc.	 6	NUI Corporation-City Gas Company of Florida			
 10	Flying J Oil & Gas Inc.	 10	Superior Natural Gas Corporation	 6	NUI Corporation-North Carolina Gas Service			
 9	Formosa Hydrocarbons Company, Inc.	 4	Syngenta AG	 6	NUI Utilities, Inc.			
 10	Gelber Group, Inc. The	 10	Tennessee Energy Acquisition Corporation	 11	Ormet Primary Aluminum Corp.			
 9	Global Octanes Texas L.P.	 11	Tesoro Petroleum Corporation	 11	Oxford Natural Gas Company			
 11	Goldston Oil Corporation	 11	Texas Energy Transfer Co	 12	Pacific Gas & Electric Company			
 11	Graphic Packaging Corporation	 10	Texex Energy Partners, Ltd.	 11	Petro-Diamond Inc.			
 8	Great River Energy	 11	Texla Energy Management Inc.	 11	Petrotex, Inc.			
 10	Gulf Gas Utilities Company	 10	The New Power Company	 11	Petsec Energy, Inc.			
 12	Hall-Houston Oil Company	 10	Tiger Natural Gas Inc.	 11	PH Exploration			
 9	Hallwood Energy Partners, LP	 10	The Oxford Oil Company	 11	Pioneer Energy Marketing Company, Inc.			
 11	Harvey Brothers Oil & Gas	 9	Torch Energy Marketing, Inc.	 12	Polsky Energy Company			
 4	Helmerich & Payne Energy Services, Inc.	 11	Torch Energy TM, Inc.	 9	Prior Energy Corporation			
 10	HESCO Gathering Company, LLC	 11	TransTexas Gas Corp.	 11	PSNC Production Corporation Inc.			
 11	Highland Energy Company	 10	TRC Operating Company, Inc.	 10	Queen Sand Resources Inc.			
 11	Hiland Partners, LLC	 11	Triad Nitrogen, Inc.	 11	R.B. Robertson & Son Oil & Gas			
 10	Houston Energy Services Company	 11	Tristar Gas Marketing Company	 11	Riverside Pipeline Company			
 11	IBEX Resources LLC	 11	Twine Gas & Power, Inc.--WMBE	 10	Sabina Blanca SL			
 11	ICC Energy Corporation - WMBE	 10	Twister Gas Services LLC	 10	San Jacinto Industrial Gas Company			
 8	Indeck Energy Services of Silver Springs, Inc.	 10	Upstream Energy Services Company, LLC	 11	Savannah Foods Industrial			
 8	Indeck-Oswego L.P.	 10	US Steel Corporation	 11	Savannah Foods & Industries, Inc.			
 11	Indeck Pepperell Power Associates	 11	Venoco, Inc.	 11	Shanghai Energy Corp.			
 11	Infinite Energy, Inc.	 6	Vermilion Resources Ltd.	 10	Shoreham Energy Services Company (Purchases Only)			
 11	Innovative Gas Services, Inc.	 10	Victoria International Ltd - WMBE.	 10	Simpson Tacoma Kraft Company			
 10	Interconn Resouces, Inc.	 11	Vista Energy Resources Inc.	 11	Smurfit-Stone Container Corporation			
 4	International Paper Company	 11	Vitol Capital Management Ltd.	 11	Southern California Edison Company			
 9	Interstate Gas Supply, Inc. 	 9	Warrior Gas Company	 11	Southern Industrial Gas Corporation			
 10	Intrepid Oil & Gas LLC	 11	Wasatch Energy LLC	 12	Southern Mineral Corp.			
 11	IP Petroleum Co., Inc.	 9	Watson Cogeneration Company	 11	Southstar Energy Services, LLC			
 7	JN Exploration and Production LP	 7	Westlake Petrochemical Corporation	 4	Southwest Airlines Co.			
 9	J Oil & Gas Inc.	 10	Westpark Resources Inc.	 11	Sport Pipeline Corp.			
 10	Jonan Gas Marketing Ltd.	 11	Wincup Holdings, Inc.	 11	Stand Energy Corp.			
 12	KCS Energy Marketing Inc.	 11	Wiser Oil Company, The	 11	Summit Natural Gas, LLP			
 12	KCS Resources, Inc.	 11	Woodward Marketing, L.L.C. 	 12	Sunoma Energy Corp.			
 11	Louisiana Municipal Natural Gas Purchasing and Dist.	 11	WTG Gas Marketing, Inc. (NO PHYSICAL DEALS)	 10	Terra Industries, Inc.			
 9	Magnum Hunter Resources Inc.	 8	Wyman-Gordon Forgings, Inc.					
 10	Mainline Energy, LLC	 11	Yates Petroleum Corporation					
 11	Makoil Inc.	  	  	  	  	  	  	
  								
 The following list represents those counterparties who are of particular concern to the RAC Credit Group. This list is not all encompassing and should be utilized in support of the Credit Policy & Procedure manual previously distributed in January 2000. For all deals which state "Call Credit for Approval", the trader must call for approval PRIOR to executing a trade. For transaction approvals please call the Credit Hotline at 3-1803. Deals involving counterparties that have not traded with ENA within the past SIX MONTHS need to call credit for approval PRIOR to executing the trade. 
Sheet2 
Sheet3 
