From:  Espinoza
Sent:  Monday, October 29, 2001 7:35 PM
To:  Brackett; Debbie R. <dbracke@enron.com>; Bradford; William
Subject:  Credit Watch List--Week of 10/29/01
Attach:  10-29-01.xls

Attached is a revised Credit Watch listing for the week of 10/29/01.   Please note that Co-Steel, Inc. was placed on "Call Credit" this week.
If there are any personnel in your group that were not included in this distribution, please insure that they receive a copy of this report.
To add additional people to this distribution, or if this report has been sent to you in error, please contact Veronica Espinoza at x6-6002.

For other questions, please contact Jason R. Williams at x5-3923,  Veronica Espinoza at x6-6002 or Darren Vanek at x3-1436.

 



***********

***********