James Vasquez  
16 Ann St. Apt.34 - Norwalk, CT 06854 - (203) 899-0236  
 
SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS  
  ➢ Extensive experience and knowledge of arbitraging power in the Mid-Continent region.  
  ➢ Strong understanding of the dynamics that influence market pricing and transmission.  
  ➢ Highly competitive, motivated and successful in high stress, multitasked environment.  
 
PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE  
 
July 2000 – June 2001  
Sempra Energy Trading, Stamford, Connecticut  
Senior Hourly Trader  
  ➢ Responsible for trading power in ECAR, FRCC, MAIN, MAPP, SERC, and SPP.  
  ➢ Oversaw the training of new hourly traders. Training consisted of understanding operational issues concerning cuts, redirecting power, TLR’s, ATC & financial bookouts and pricing issues such as factoring the cost of transmission, ancillaries and line losses into the total price of power.  
  ➢ Coordinated third party in-house training programs on OATI services and operational issues related to the grid.  
  ➢ Designed spreadsheets and implemented procedures to assist in pricing power and determining transmission/megawatt requirements to transport power.  
  ➢ Assisted back office in reconciling trade discrepancies.  
  ➢ Other duties include trading next day off-peak in Cinergy and AEP, resupplying cuts and formulating strategies for next day hourly trading.  
 
February 1996 – June 2000  
Statoil Energy, Inc., Alexandria, Virginia  
Senior Transmission Analyst, Wholesale Structure September 1998 – June 2000  
  ➢ Developed the expertise required to transport power in an effort to take advantage of arbitrage opportunities in the northeast.  
  ➢ Structured transmission deals in the secondary markets.  
  ➢ Oversaw the operational issues of converting a generation plant to merchant status in PJM and established the procedures to dispatch the unit.  
  ➢ Trained operations desk on OASIS (PJM, NYPP, NEPOOL, ECAR, SERC and MAIN), ISO-NE Market Systems, OATI’s E-tagging system and how to access/interpret real time information from PJM and ISO-NE systems.  
 
Wholesale Analyst, East Coast Trading Desk January 1998 – September 1998  
  ➢ Facilitated wholesale trading in PJM, ECAR, and SERC by scheduling spot and forward trades.  
  ➢ Managed retail loads in New York and PJM.  
  ➢ Initiated the execution of all blanket transmission contracts in PJM, ECAR, NEPOOL, New York, SERC, and MAIN.  
    
   Wholesale Gas Analyst February 1996 – January 1998  
  ➢ Responsible for nominating Tennessee, PanHandle, Transco, Tetco and Algonquin pipelines.  
  ➢ Other responsibilities included buying and selling capacity.  
 
January 1994 – June 1995  
Trahan & Partners Real Estate Valuation and Consulting, Houston, Texas  
Junior Appraiser  
    
   July 1991 – May 1992  
   Hertz Equipment Corporation, Houston, Texas  
   Sales Coordinator  
 
  EDUCATION  
Texas A&M University, College Station, Texas  
Master’s Degree, Land Economics and Real Estate, December 1993  
Bachelor of Business Administration, Marketing, May 1991  
 
 
 