NomLogic Simulation  
Pipeline(s): See attached list  
 
Counterparty(s): Enron North America & Dynegy Energy Resources Limited Partnership  
 
Enron Trader  
 
Login to the SITARA Stage environment. Enter SITARA deals for the counterparties and pipeline(s) listed above. Enter multiple deals based on the following parameters:  
 
Location Assignments:  
    ➢ Without a meter (pipeline/zone location only)  
    ➢ With ONE or MANY meters assigned at the SITARA Deal Volume level  
    ➢ With ONE or MANY meters assigned at the SITARA BAV Volume level  
 
Counterparty Names:  
    ➢ Enter 3rd party deals using the counterparty names listed above  
    ➢ Enter desk-to-desk deals on the pipelines listed above  
 
Deal Edits:  
    ➢ Mid-simulation, make changes to a selection of deals entered  
    ➢ Change various items (price, volumes, locations, etc.)  
    ➢ Kill at least one deal during the simulation  
 
Enron Scheduler  
 
Login:  
    ➢ Login to SITARA Stage-Start: Programs: Training Apps: SITARA Training stage: SITARA Launchpad: userid-cslagle, password-cslagle  
    ➢ Login to UNIFY Stage- Start: Programs: Development Apps: Test Applications: UNIFY: UNIFY Gas Power-Test: userid-cslagle, password-0454  
    ➢ Set-up desktop as normal for pipelines listed above  
    ➢ Login to NomLogic: stage.commoditylogic.com; userid-CL692031: password: carrie0454  
 
Monitor new deals/changed deals:  
    ➢ Monitor SITARA Deal Ticker  
    ➢ Monitor NomLogic Deal List  
 
Communicate with customers:  
    ➢ Edit deals via NomLogic Deal Dialog/Deal Edits window  
    ➢ Complete the communication/nomination process for all deals entered during simulation  
 
Third Party Scheduler  
 
Login:  
    ➢ Login to SITARA Stage-Start: Programs: Training Apps: SITARA Training stage: SITARA Launchpad: userid-cslagle, password-cslagle  
    ➢ Set-up desktop as normal for pipelines listed above  
    ➢ Login to NomLogic: stage.commoditylogic.com; userid-CL692031: password: carrie0454  
 
Monitor new deals/changed deals:  
    ➢ Monitor SITARA Deal Ticker  
    ➢ Monitor NomLogic Deal List  
 
Communicate with Enron scheduler:  
    ➢ Edit deals via NomLogic Deal Dialog/Deal Edits window  
    ➢ Split deals with ONE or MANY meters, if possible  
    ➢ Split deals with ONE or MANY psnas  
    ➢ Complete the communication/nomination process for all deals entered during simulation  
 