 Registry Update
 FAQs
 What does it do?
 The file will update two user settings in the Windows registry. These settings are MaxConnectionsPerServer 
 and MaxConnectionsPer1_0Server. The values for these settings will be updated to 80 in each case. This is the 
 recommended setting for Internet Explorer v5. Some users who have used previous versions of IE may lack 
 these settings or have lower values for these settings. 
 Why do it?
 Commodity Logic uses multiple server connections to achieve real time updates of data to the NomLogic 
 screens. If these settings are too low, users may experience poor performance in the NomLogic application.
 Who needs to do it?
 NomLogic users who experience poor performance in the applicaiton.
 Will every new user have to do this?
 Many users will already have sufficient settings and will not encounter a problem. This is provided as a 
 temporary fix during the Beta period. Commodity Logic is preparing a change to the application to make this 
 seamless to users in the future.
 What if these instructions don't work for me?
 Some users in corporate settings may lack sufficient administrative rights to update their registry. In such 
 cases, the user will have to seek assistance from their IT department to update the registry settings.
 1. Click on the file CommodityLogicUpdate.reg
 2. Windows will display a dialog box asking if you want to update your registry. *
 Press 'Yes' 
 3. If the update is succcessful, you will see a confirmation.
