From:  Tycholiz  Barry <Barry.Tycholiz@ENRON.com>
Sent:  Friday, August 10, 2001 1:49 PM
To:  Dasovich  Jeff <Jeff.Dasovich@ENRON.com>
Subject:  RE: Socal Storage Projects

Thanks Jeff,  I am planning a business trip to San Fransisco with Stephanie Miller towrards the end of August... are you around. 

I will check on dates but it should be the end of Aug. 

BT 

 -----Original Message-----
From: 	Dasovich, Jeff  
Sent:	Thursday, August 09, 2001 2:02 PM
To:	Tholt, Jane M.; Tycholiz, Barry; Lawner, Leslie
Subject:	RE: Socal Storage Projects

They are selling gas from Montebello.  

They have been given authority by the PUC to begin taking steps to sell from the remaining two (Alsio and La Goleta), but the PUC left some issues (principally around ratemaking) open, and have not given them the authority to actually begin selling the gas.  SoCal would like to start selling around Oct. 1, so they're expecting (hoping for) a decision in early September.  However, the state-run consumer group (ORA) and TURN have asked the Commission to require SoCal to retain two-thirds of the gas and sell it to the core at book value--unclear where the Commission will come out on that.

If there's anything else, let me know.

Best,
Jeff

 -----Original Message-----
From: 	Tholt, Jane M.  
Sent:	Thursday, August 09, 2001 10:44 AM
To:	Dasovich, Jeff
Subject:	Socal Storage Projects

Can you provide the West Desk with an update on the Socal Storage projects-Socal Montebello Salvage Project ;Alsio Canyon and Lo goleta Cushion Gas Projects  Would like to  have something by this afternoon if possible.
  


***********

***********